Finding Aid for Ann Arbor Book Festival records, 2003-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Ann Arbor Book Festival records 2003-2010
Ann Arbor Book Festival.
5 linear feet
2012137 Aa 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were received from the Festival organization (donor no. 10729 ) and came to the library in February 2012.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The Ann Arbor Book Festival organization was established in 2003; the first festival was held in 2004. The mission of the festival was to promote reading, to showcase authors and poets (many from Michigan), and to draw attention to the challenge of literacy in the local community. Members of the board of directors and the advisory board were comprised of book store owners, library administrators, local presses, and community people. The first festival extended four days and included lectures, book signings, and exhibitor booths.
The records of the Festival document the management of the yearly event. The records are largely maintained by year and include program of events, publicity and promotional material, scheduling information, minutes of meetings, advisory board agenda, grant applications and other financial information, and snapshot photographs of events.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor Book Festival.; Festivals--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Event files
  - 2004 (Box 1)
  - 2005 (Box 1)
  - 2006 (Box 2)
  - 2007 (Box 3)
  - 2008 (Box 4)
  - 2009 (Box 4)
- Other materials
  - Record book, 2004-2010 (mainly 2008-2010) (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 5)
  - Corporate materials: include 501(C)(3) applications, by-laws, application for grant, contracts, and related, 1 expandable folder (Box 5)
  - Photographic snapshots (and CD-Rs of photographs) of events, panels, banners, street views, 1 expandable folder (Box 5)